

SAMUKELE NDLOVU

SOFTWARE
DEVELOPER, WEB
DESIGNER

CONTACT

() 072 395 8208

samukele107@gmail.com

<u>HyperionDev</u>

GitHub

Einkedin

PROFILE

I am a software developer with a passion for building high-quality software applications. I have more than 3 years of experience in the field, I am well-versed in software development methodologies such as Agile and Scrum. I enjoy playing computer games and travelling.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

HTML & CSS. Python. Django Bootstrap. Javascript. Angular.

Aligulai.

Wordpress.

Other Skills Include

Performance Optimization. Installing and configuring computer hardware and software.

Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks. Troubleshooting and Quality Control.

EDUCATION

Matric - 2015

Hyperiondev - Software Engineering (2022-2023)

Udemy - Python for Data Science and Machine Learning

CodeX - Attended 2 weeks bootcamp on Javascript

Freecodecamp (online) - Basic CSS,HTML,JAVASCRIPT, and Python Programming(2020-2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company: A1 Group

Sales Agent (2018 - 2021)

Technical Support Agent (2022 - current)

My role include providing Technical services to clients, I am responsible in assisting clients with technical issues and providinng effective troubleshooting steps, which may include use of diagnostic tools and softwares. I also log client queries and complaints.

Company: Eventar (eventar.co.za)

Web developer, Product Architecture (2021 - current

I am part of the creative team that developed Eventar. A platform where all event vendors showcase their work to customers all in one platform. My role include updating & maintaining of the website and Designing on layout

August Roots Healthcare

Web developer(Part-time: 2022 - current)

I provide maintainance to the Website and updating layouts of the Website

CONTACT

() 072 395 8208

samukele107@gmail.com

SAMUKELE NDLOVU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, WEB DESIGNER

I am a self-taught software developer with a strong passion for coding and problem-solving. My love for technology started at a young age, and I have spent countless hours studying programming languages, practicing coding challenges, and building personal projects.

Although I don't have a traditional computer science degree, I have developed a deep understanding of programming concepts and best practices through my self-study and i have furthered my knowlegde and skills through bootcamps and have rewarded with certifications. I have experience in various programming languages such as Python and JavaScript, I am comfortable working with both front-end and back-end development frameworks.